(Amy:)Okay, so how do you feel
about party balloons?
(Sheldon:)Uh, Mylar balloons, yes.
(Sheldon:)Latex balloons, no.
(Sheldon:)Water balloons,
I will jump off the roof
(Sheldon:)and aim for your car.
(Penny:)All right, what about music?
(Sheldon:)I enjoy marching bands
(Sheldon:)and Tibetan throat singing.
(Penny:)No music it is.
(Bernadette:)What kind of cake
do you like?
Well, my favorite is chocolate
with strawberry frosting,
(Sheldon:)three layers,
and if there's
(Sheldon:)writing on it,
make sure it's not all caps.
(Sheldon:)I don't need my dessert
yelling at me.
(Raj:)Hey, so what was
Adam West like on the phone?
(Leonard:)Uh, nice guy.
(Leonard:)But it was a little weird
to hear Batman say,
“Don't ring the doorbell
or my poodles will go crazy.”
(Raj:)You know, Adam West
is my favorite Batman?
(Scene:)Well,
(Raj:)after Michael Keaton,
Christian Bale
(Raj:)and Batman from
The Lego Movie.
(Howard:)Don't say that to him.
(Raj:)What?
He beat out George Clooney.
(Raj:)And that's something.